[Music]
hey how's it going Alex good how are you
thanks for having me yeah pretty good
thanks so much for for joining us uh you
know a little early your time
whereabouts are you I am in Berkeley
oh very nice very nice that's good
that's good so uh so yeah how did bits
and Bobs kind of come about actually was
I was i r in that yeah it's um so I have
this the the compendium which is that
sort of custom web app I built over the
last number of years to organize my
thoughts and if you look at the
compendium live you'll think that it's
dead I haven't added anything to it for
years I actually add have it open every
day and I have I add hundreds of notes
to it every day in my private working
notes area I use embeddings to help me
find alties across different ideas and
then each week I go and spend a few
hours on the weekends when the kids are
napping and I distill out the the notes
from that week that resonate with me and
I developed them a little bit and it
started off actually as a uh believe it
or not as a practice I um very early
version of it was when I used to report
to Clay bore um who recently founded
that um Sierra with Brett Taylor uh I
would send a email on Monday to him of
like here's the people I'm meeting with
here's the like things that my I'm doing
and here's a few takeaways like
interesting ideas I think you might find
relevant and I I continueed that
practice at stripe and uh and then I
kind of that section got deeper and
deeper and deeper and longer and longer
and longer and I started sharing it with
more and more people in my internal
little strategy study groups and then
into internal blogs and then I started
publishing external I do you know I
would do all that reflection on my own
personal time and uh yeah so uh now it's
a document that has a stupid number of
pages in it and the it's really slow one
of the things that happens is people
when they're searching in it um it takes
so long to load that they're searching
and it will Google Docs will kind of
think that they're typing into the
document and they'll so it suggest a
random edit to the document because
they're actually just searching for
something in the document so it happens
like once a day um I think I'm probably
gonna split it's like I think 700 Pages
or so and I again I add like 20 Pages or
so a week which is yeah just silly yeah
I know it's probably one of the stress
test totally so we're gonna get into
talking about the future but uh Curious
actually to kind of start with the the
past a little bit like with this round
of you know AI uh and you know kind of
gen AI uh came around when did this
first hit home for you like were you
super skeptical at first and you know
was there a bit of an aha moment that
got you thinking like maybe there's
something real here yeah I I've been
following obviously all the papers and
interesting developments at Google
research and others for many years and
watching it kind of slowly plot along
and some of the silly things that people
were doing with the earlier version of
chat Bots and the the moment really hit
home for me though is I I have a a few
groups of people I facilitate of
interesting thinkers I just like talking
to and and kind of having collaborative
debate with and once a year or so we
would get an Airbnb in the woods and we
would go and we just have a few days
like 12 people just for an interesting
long-term discussion about what's going
to happen in the next decade um about
crypto and not just for crypto but for
all of society and then the next year we
did generative Ai and that was I think a
few weeks before chat gbt came out and
we had a number of folks you know good
friends people who you know as well and
um in the session it's just like three
days of just thinking and pulling on
threads and afterwards I would sit down
and I would just like write 60 pages of
like here's what I took away from that
discussion and I remember writing down
and be like holy like this is going
to change everything and it's on the
cusp of it it so many things change that
people haven't even realized yet and uh
and then a few weeks later tat PT comes
out and it was like just like you know
starting Bell for everybody and I knew
at that point that like this was going
to be like you know lmms are not some
flash in the pan they are not some
random technology like they are a
fundamental disruptive innovation and I
think you need to act like it I think a
lot of people are acting like AI as a
sustaining Innovation and I don't think
that's true at all I think it radically
changes a number of things that we
haven't even we're like Wy coyote out
over the cliff kind of as a as an
industry we're like oh we're just going
to slap some eye on this it's like
that's not how that works at all
actually changes fundamentally the way
that we write software the way that we
can um we can experience things and it
it changes the cost structures of
everything it's really interesting and
fascinating thing but it was that yeah
it was that period right before chat TBD
came out that I was like oh wow uh oh
you know got it that's awesome um so
this event is called you know AI native
Dev and I'm it's it's be a little bit of
a double on Tundra can mean different
things I'm curious what what that what
that means for you I think people are
currently attempting they're just
jamming AI on the sides of the way that
they built software before and the way
that they would approach problems and I
think when you embrace llms you write
software differently and you think of it
it's almost like how do you pull the
software out of the like you know mind
of this llm and you do it um in a way
that's not like a you know traditional
collaborating with another person you do
it a lot more like what Tesla's doing I
think of like specs and this designing a
thing like I had a um simp silly little
example um there's this game called Sky
Joe that's a fun little card game and we
were playing it and I got really into it
I realized oh if you could count the
cards going through you would have a
better you could strategically be making
better calls and so I wanted to make a
little little thing a little web app to
make it so you could uh just keep track
of the cards had been played out of the
deck and it would tell you the the
probabilties of different cards coming
up or whatever this is the kind of thing
that would have taken me a few hours on
a weekend uh to like sit down like you
know create a new um project from
scratch and like slowly add in stuff and
what I did instead was I built it in
like 10 minutes and I just used
anthropic artifacts and I did exactly
the way I would have done it I said
first write a little function that does
this okay now put that function in this
now add typescript typing that allows
like now like I just sort of told it
what I would have done from each of the
individual steps and in 10 minutes you
have this really nice nicely styled
thing that has undo and save and all
these little features and I built it by
like not by writing any code but by just
coaxing it in the right order with the
right steps uh and kind of things I
wanted to do and that was that felt like
you know radically different way of
building software to me than WR sitting
down and writing the silly little hobby
project that would have taken me you
know a few hours to do right yeah do you
think that that kind of app like this
notion of a you know I think some people
like micro apps and the like is
gonna you know change the the way that a
bunch of even kind of like users and
non-developers kind of maybe even kind
of getting into this world where they
can scratch their own itches where like
at the moment maybe they just like I
could do spreadsheet so I try and use a
spreadsheet to do everything that I can
and like they have these different tools
but they don't feel like they can create
custom software
I think it will but um for a couple
reasons so I was a friend of mine is not
particularly Technical and I knew I was
super in playing around with AI and they
said I want to like see what it can do I
want to have it programmed so we went to
chat gbt and they were saying a thing
they wanted to do and then they would
give it the HTML and I would copy and
paste it into a thing and then load it
into a separate Tab and that step
mystified him he like I don't understand
what's happening and the feedback loop
just took enough time to like copy paste
and then sometimes it would tell you you
had to kind of surgically put it back in
code back into the because it would only
update a small portion of it and then we
switched to anthropic that has artifacts
and that was basically the same Loop
just in a live preview and that
radically changed it instead of it
feeling of me handholding him he just
sat there and was doing little things
and experimenting with it and I I left I
came back 20 minutes later and he built
a relatively complex little little toy
app and uh he was like I guess I'm a
programmer now I was like I guess yeah
sure like it just but it felt like this
immediacy I think felt really really
nice I think by default what we'll see
with AI uh in the current distribution
physics is we'll see a proliferation of
both hyper centralized hyper aggregators
and a profusion of lots of little micro
apps that are like little toys that they
don't really do that much on their own I
think the real trick will be how can you
get figure out a system that allows
these micro apps to add up to something
much larger than some of other parts to
interact with other micro apps and other
experiences and have this emergent
possibility that's quite challenging I
think that requires like a fundamentally
different kind of like substrate uh to
be built on and that's one of the things
that we're working on but I do think
that it's
a you know so much of software so much
of the industry is B predicated the idea
that software is expensive to write and
cheap to run and llms mess with both of
these assumptions because code that uses
llms to execute which is not all code in
the future but like you know a fair bit
of it uh that now has a marginal cost
that is above zero which means it is
expensive uh in some significant way
that we're not used to um and
secondarily uh LMS are really good at
writing crappy software on demand for
basically free so like it's not good
software often unless you have the right
structures and approaches and the right
kind of scaffolding to make sure that
it's doing the thing that you wanted
like what you all are building um but it
is a uh and that these radically change
kind of how we think of where you would
apply software and how you would apply
it clay Sher has this old essay from I
think it's 2007 called situated software
and it's now off the internet yet GN has
a mirror of it it's a great essay and it
talks about situated software and
software that is situated to a hypers
specific context so anytime you've
written the spreadsheet formula it's
situated software it's situated
specifically in the context of this
particular spreadsheet and anytime that
someone looks at someone else's bit of
situated software they go that's piece
of crap it barely works it's insecure
it's ugly but to the person who built it
it's perfect it does exactly and
precisely what they need and sometimes
in those contexts actually you know say
what happens that breakes say I don't
know I'll just slap some more situated
software on the side and especially when
LM can help you write the situated
software you can get software that's
just right it's just the right size for
you as opposed to this you know one size
fits none software that we have today in
our modern era yeah that makes sense so
some people I see kind of uh snarky
about you know I can just do these
little toy things right like you stay in
your Zone stay in the micro apps uh era
you're not going to you know I'm an
amazing expert developer and you're
never going to be a to touch me and the
domain that I understand and my
enterprise software and the like how do
you think over time especially like llms
are actually going to be a to help you
know in very broad ways across of the
spectrum of development that's that's
out there or do you think it will never
oh it for sure and I think folks like
tesl and others are are really pushing
the limits of what you can get I think
the big story by the way the last year
people talk about the quality
improvements to me it's the context
length improvements that just radically
changes the kinds of questions you could
ask you know if you wanted to ask before
of a of a large book um you know what
are the major themes of this book you
can't answer it with rag it's not
possible because it's not like there's
like this is the theme and like that's
in the embedding like you have to have a
broad context and the more that you have
this broad context the more that you can
see these subtle patterns keep track of
and understand where things are going
and so I feel like we're just beginning
stages of figuring out how to get llms
to build um uh large bits of software I
also think one things that I think
excited about Tesla's approach is um
lm's one of their superpowers are really
really really good at translation and uh
you can translate English to code and so
before you know like the spec is not
just some little documentation it
actually is almost the primary semantic
thing and the actual code is kind of
like you know I think of like compiling
the spec into code you know and it's
it's unlike a normal compiler where like
you know everyone who learned see at the
beginning certain point says the
compiler is broken it's like ah I can
guarantee you this compiler is not
broken for for this case so you learn
that the compiler is almost always
trustworthy with llms like it can get
confused and the thing it gets confused
on most is when it's not uh it's not
high locality of the code when it's kind
of in multiple files it has to
coordinate based on a specific phrase or
word that has to be consistent in these
multiple places LMS tend to kind of get
a little bit confused by that that kind
of situation but there's ways of adding
baffing and you know idioms to make it
so they are more likely to stay to a
pretty good answer yeah I think one of
my realizations around this was feeling
like I was using English to poke at
things just like you were talking about
but then all of that information was
lost it was like in the chat session and
it was gone and it was like but that was
like my actual requir like yeah
recording steps of things to get to the
the that result yeah right why am I so
it felt like I'm compiling this thing
and then just taking my compiled output
with me yeah like wait a minute isn't
the other thing the important thing to
stare around so what if that could be
the canonical piece instead and like and
so that's why specs kind of made a lot
of sense um to me um as you poked around
with all these things what have you
found you've mentioned some of these
like llms to be particularly good at or
bad at when it comes to you know coding
and development in general I one way I
think about this is is like you know in
Jurassic Park when they have there have
gaps in the dinosaur DNA and it fills it
in with frog DNA kind of llms do that
too where if you don't bring the
specific examples it just kind of
assumes based on the most generic
background information of how it fits in
so they do really well if your thing
looks like if you're if you're writing
it in the same kind of react style that
everybody else writes it they're really
good of that uh because they've got tons
of frog DNA to bring into your
particular situation uh to get really
good results if you're writing an
algorithm that's been represented is
like nicely cleanly separated and SE and
exists in lots of tutorials and
Wikipedia articles or whatever they're
also pretty good at reproducing that um
when you have like an architecture like
a relatively large architecture that is
slightly a atypical and has some weird
you know stylistic and calling you know
ways it's been designed architected they
start getting a little bit funky there
and a little bit like they can lose the
plot a bit remember that like llms can't
count and the and so uh it's kind of a
miracle in some ways that they they work
reason that they can handle some of
these cases one of the reasons like
really deeply nested Json they lose
track of like wait wait am I in like an
object context or an array context and
they'll like kind of Mis Nest some of
the things partially because it's just
really hard to keep track of the
counting like one way looking at this is
they do a really good job of they seeing
objects like that so smaller chunks of
Json they're shaped roughly like that
there's been way more examples because
like they the the presumably the Json
you'd see on the web has a logarithmic
kind of fallof of like the the larger
sizes get increasingly less less common
and so it doesn't have as much training
data to keep track of and it it can't
fundamentally count and so it just kind
of loses track of and just it's remember
it's all like Vibes spased programming
it's just it's Vibes are extremely
dialed in yeah and it's fascinating
because like you mentioned like you know
there's a a lot of react code on the
internet that has ended up you know in
these models and the like and then I
start to think about you the frog DNA
it's like do we have the kind of me frog
because most of the DNA that's got it in
there with react code is from kind of
the average react developer not like the
react core developer that's out there
and so like is there like that magical
you know piece of like actually the
shark DNA that hasn't evolved that much
right it's like it's just gotten really
good and HED in and so you really want
something that's good
enough uh that it's got enough content
that's out there but is is also really
uh kind of focused like I'm really
curious about the notion of also just
kind of like King making as well like if
we created a brand new language today do
we have a chance to make it uh and how
do you feel how do you think about kind
of the role of data and quality data and
golden path data all of those things
with llms I love the shark DNA I just
writing that down the uh yeah I don't
know it's it uh
lmms are really good at imitation
they're so insanely good at imitation
that it sometimes looks like Innovation
but they're really fundamentally kind of
conceptually interpolating across just a
very wide swath of uh Human Experience
and examples and uh that does feel like
it pulls us towards the Cent it pulls us
TOS the average mushy Center like when
you in its writing its default writing
style is like corporate speak because
that's the mushy Center that at the be
at the core like the the random Bland
heat death average kind of and we get
the same thing in in programming where
just kind of like I use react I'm just
do it whatever the most basic way you
can possibly like basic in the you know
in the perjorative sense and um I do
think it it one thing that's interesting
and challenging like one of the ways it
knows how to wait what things are good
is like things that have worked for
others in the past are more likely to be
replicated and other people to also talk
about them and write about them and so
LMS aren't random sampling all texts
that could exist they're random sampling
the text that humans have found found
useful enough to propagate right and so
you have this natural thing where humans
are selecting to some degree the thing
that's that's reading off of and uh but
over time as more and more that
selection is done from like this just
basian kind of averaging process you
kind of lose some of that signal and it
does feel like it will pull us more
towards the centroid it also does feel
like to me it will be much much harder
to escape local Maxima uh because it's
just in default by default if you if I
don't have a strong opinion about how to
write this bit of code and I said I do a
thing that has this Behavior what's it
going to reach for it's going to reach
for the most obvious obvious basic
answer of that and put it in there and I
don't have a strong opinion so I'm not
gonna go through no no no no do it in
this other you know style that I think
is interesting uh and so that's fine and
so now you'll have yet another piece
that is now put onto the whole
collection of uh of um yeah that's funny
now I'm thinking about how to nudge
selection to be like this software passs
passes tests a lot
like what are the other parts of
selection that could help um nudge
things for for us um so I've noticed in
the past you've mentioned that uh uh you
know spending time to Define
requirements saves extraordinary amounts
of time uh and so I'm just curious what
what does requirement just like when we
talk about specs it's like oh it means
lots of different things to different
people like what do you mean by that
um uh sorry I'm just taking it out uh
okay I'm just this is how I write I just
take notes from interesting things you
will say and I write them down the um I
think it's part partially that one my
direct experience in the last few weeks
and I've realized it's a pattern I've
seen many times like oh we understand
how to build this I've got the idea in
my head we will simply execute this it
turns out explaining the requirements
like you have like this hyper object in
your head of like oh this should work
and all the pieces and like this and
explaining to other people is like
serialization process it takes so long
and it's like it's like comori kind of
thing to really serialize it perfectly
and the way to communicate it is then
factor that serialization into higher
level requirements which is a process
that takes a ton of time and so you're
always like oh we're fine we're fine
we're just gonna we're just gonna wing
it I'm just gonna give them enough
guidance or whatever but if you do this
improperly you're like oh we'll go fast
by not doing the requirements or
factoring out the the work of
requirements and then what you end up
with is you realize later that people
didn't understand the fundamental thing
you were trying to do and they went in
these other weird corners and you have
to like no no actually there's a whole
thing you can't do it that way you gotta
do it this way and they go okay cool I
had to throw out this entire thing I
just did now and so to them it feels
like a total thrash and the mental model
in my head is like a d a dynamic
programming problem without memorization
done in exactly the wrong order so each
calculation you're doing you know 20
time 30 30 times or whatever and that's
what it feels like to do the
requirements like to me the requirements
process is taking the serialization of
the hyper object and then distilling it
into a more um uh abstract and condensed
version that can be efficiently
communicated to somebody else yeah that
makes sense so uh some developers kind
of initially got excited about having
these new tours some developers got a
little bit nervous at first of like you
know is AI going to take my job right
that that whole meme when you look ahead
five 10 years out there like what
aspects do you think of software
development are going to remain
fundamentally hum driven uh and what
parts do you think we're going to be
somewhat happy to uh to pass over to be
AI driv yeah and I think that I'm
personally excited about AI as a tool
for human creativity because it takes
the like the Bland drudgery and allows
you to like handle like it to handle
those parts the parts that aren't
exciting or aren't interesting aren't um
surprising to you in any way it just
kind of allows you to execute on those
way way faster and you know what one of
the powers of infrastructure in general
one of the reasons infrastructure works
and creates value in the world is
instead of every single individual
customer having to build their own lower
layers you can build it once and share
it across many you write it once you
share it with many so everybody's
getting that value but the cost is a
single instance of it so you're
factoring out the most boring parts of
people a lots of people's jobs llms also
factor out the most boring Parts the
parts that are just the mundane drudgery
and I think that if you use them
properly and see them as a tool to
extend your creativity they allow you to
to do other interesting new things like
I've heard a number of people have told
me they've started writing poetry you
know and they're like yeah I just I used
to like it in like high school I haven't
done it in a while and now I've got like
a a brainstorming writing partner that
helps me you know come up with a better
rhyme for that or F eight different
examples of this or like critique the
thing with like if I show The Poetry
even to my spouse like I don't want to
show them like shitty writer like and uh
so I know I think it's those kinds of
things that allow people to stretch
further and
I think that it's an active Choice it is
also just as easy to take those tools
and become increasingly passive and
increasingly um like cool now have to
think it very hard no no I think you
should use these tools to help you think
harder you know yeah that makes sense um
so we both spent a lot of our uh careers
uh on the working on the web platform uh
as we mentioned at the beginning uh and
I think we both had a uh a love towards
the kind of openness of that era and
then we got to see mobile which uh you
know guy mentioned this guo mentioned
this in the Kino was uh slightly
different shape of uh of openness which
had different uh effects as someone who
like really studies ecosystem Dynamics
and the like how do you think um AI is
gonna you know potentially change the
landscape as it comes to like what can
happen to the existing you know
ecosystems like how's this going to
affect the web and mo about and like
what opportunities it maybe give us in
the future to to to have change yeah I
think that typically the like
decentralization centralization is like
a Tik Tok it's at the beginning stage of
a new disruptive Paradigm it's open and
decentralized and later it centralizes
as the best patterns are found and
become like the compounding advantage to
the ones who are best at it get stronger
and stronger and stronger and you get to
a really boring part with that there's
just everything interesting has been
done like there's no space for
Innovation it's just I don't know if one
of these three big players think that
it's allowed to exist it's allowed to
exist like that's insane to me um and so
I think my that's one of my hopes of AI
as a disruptive innovation is that it
resets and gives you into this open
ended uh decentralized world to start
again um I think in some ways AI there
was a real danger a number like a year
and a half ago I thought that uh AI
would be an inherently centralizing
technology it's so Capital intensive
that like only a very small number of
companies can possibly invest the
capital and then now they become the
only ones that can you know train and
host these large models and that was a
very real possibility like I think
looking at like a year and a half ago
there was a real real possibility that
um open AI would just be the hyper
aggregator the Apex aggregator to rule
them all in this new world and we jump
straight from centralized to hyper
centralized and like that would be it
and I think very encouragingly for
society one anthropic built a better
model like uh you know Claude 3.5 uh you
know Sonet 3.5 is my daily driver I use
it every day I use it all the time um
it's like arguably a better model on a
number of fronts which means now there's
another at least there's multiple horses
in the race Gemini has been making a lot
of really interesting progress and then
Zuckerberg comes along and M just goes
hey here's an open weights model that is
actually one of the best in class which
really scrambles all the Dynamics in a
really healthy way they mean that I
think happens now is instead of the AI
model producers having this extreme
centralizing force they look a lot more
like to me like um cell network
providers of extremely Capital intensive
and also not that much pricing power
because they're basically Commodities
and you have lots of different options
to pick pick from which is I think
really beneficial for society because
those individual operators don't have
that much strategic power but all of us
benefit from there being nice
competition and allows an open ecosystem
to to thrive on top of that one of the
bets I was asserting you know a year ago
is companies that take AI for granted
can do some really interesting things if
you are fighting to build Frontier
models that compete with the big ones
like wow that is a really tough space to
be in but if you say I'm just going to
assume that there's going to be good
competition and there will be multiple
good cheap options to pick from that you
know competition will drive the quality
up and the cost down consistently that's
a pretty safe assumption I don't care
who wins I don't care which ones of
these do better I just know that like
there will be good high quality cheap
models to use and that seems like a
pretty safe assumption at this point
which allows an open ecosystem on top
which I think is enormously exciting for
society yeah that makes sense and then
another thing that I love about the web
ecosystem um is browser extensions of
all things like it felt like you've got
this aftermarket kind of approach where
like I can come along and someone can
build a thing that changes the thing for
for me and do you think AI ecosystems
are going to allow for maybe a more
personal custom experiences that I I can
maybe experience you know the streamyard
system that I'm in now with like a few
different tweaks without having to
persuade that company to make that
change for me which obviously doesn't
scale I think so and I think you know I
I think back to gree monkey I think gree
monkey was one of like the golden eras
of the of the browser of like these
little scripts that you could put in and
one of my good friends is Euston users
scs.org which was the kind of
centralized Community for that and uh I
think gree monkey was really powerful
the problem with gree monkey ultimately
was it was insecure and fundamentally so
and so even as a Savvy user um choosing
a set of scripts to in your thing
there's like a there's a there's a curve
that looks like this like I only install
10 of these because I have to really
trust that they aren't going to mess
with my Gmail or like sell my data or
whatever and I think the trick is how
can you get that kind of thing and I
would never tell my dad to install it my
God can you imagine what terrible crazy
stuff he would have installed with you
know and running a grease monkey so how
do you change the security and privacy
model to make it so that actually it's
just a purely like yep keep on going and
the sky is the limit and everybody
should um be able to tweak I think
that's possible but requires a uh
thinking about the security and privacy
models it can't just be like duct taped
on to the existing privacy models got it
makes sense okay I noticed there's some
questions uh that have been asked here
so I want to get to them so I don't take
all of your time so Min asked how does a
developer new to create an a micro app
Ure that the code creators created is of
good quality and safe they known
techniques to use when interacting with
an llm this is one of the things that is
uh why micro apps are useful in this
context uh if you certain code it's
compiled you know if it compiles there's
a pretty good chance that at least does
something correct and like this is like
a this also by the way is a nice Loop
for llms of like if it doesn't compile
you sell it back to the llm here was the
code you gave me here's the compile
error fix it and it it can do a pretty
good job that's like kind of automated
spoke testing um the problem is like the
semantics to get the semantics of the
thing correct and one of the nice things
about micro apps and one of the reasons
they're a sweet spot is because you can
just poke at it and you poke the five
buttons in the right order does it do
the thing I expected there's not too
many like the comori space of
possibilities isn't that large but you
have to Goble to interact with it and
poke at it and go yeah that does the
thing I wanted or nope wait a second it
I hit this button and it did thing
that's wrong try again LM but like the
bigger it gets the more likely that
you've gotten something uh has gotten
something wrong and that's where the
importance of testing becomes
extraordinarily important and I think
one of the reasons that what you all are
doing is really interesting is if you
write the spec it's also easy to write
the tests um and I find that like the
biggest reason people don't write tests
in practice because it's really it's
such a log and it's such a pain in the
butt and you're it's you're doing it in
a way that feels very different than
right in that code it you only attacks
but is the thing that allows you to go
fast later well llms also are honestly
they don't get bored they're totally
willing to write the boring annoying uh
tests and like maybe it's not exactly
correct but it's more likely to catch a
thing that is wrong in the future and
like maybe you dive into go oh wait this
test was kind of wrong but that's the
thing that gives you that smoke the
smoke test that helps you know that I
should dive in and try to debug you know
yeah okay Anthony asked what are the
best examples you've seen of stringing
together micro apps or their functions
incumbent today like zapia for workflows
comes to mind I think we are not even in
the first inning of this I feel like so
far we're seeing really interesting
stuff like get up spark is interesting
and obviously anthropic artifacts was
interesting and uh what vercel is doing
with vzer is super interesting um but
these are all individual micro apps um
they aren't even distributable
necessarily like the for anthropy it's
like it's almost an afterthought you can
distribute the artifact and others you
can't and so I don't think we we know
what good looks like in this yet uh I
think that there is a uh because we
haven't even started we like we as a as
an eosm discovered that uh micro apps
are a sweet spot for llms but we haven't
yet figured out like what to do with
that okay in a world of lots of microps
how do you stitch them together I think
that's an open question that we're still
no one has really got to good have on
yet yeah awesome well Alex thanks so
much for taking the time I could talk to
you for hours about this stuff it's been
really fun um and uh yeah find uh find
Alex online can't wait to hear more
about uh your startup it's called common
tools is that right y yeah super excited
about that and uh yeah join the Discord
and ask questions there too and and
we'll be looking over it but Alex thanks
so much of course great to seeing you
thanks for having me cheers